Guide to the Jobs With Justice Records 2001-2012
Jobs With Justice Records
- E8: National Coalitions and Campaigns (Box 24)
  - NPP Report and Briefing, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Privatization versus the Public Interest (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Grassroots Leadership, Privatization Research Project, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Grassroots Policy Project, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - CLUE, Los Angeles (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Center for Economic and Policy Research, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Center for Economic Justice, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - NAFTA, GAH Citizens Trade Campaign, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - National Immigration Forum, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - National Immigration Law Center, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Taskforce, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - National Farm Worker Ministry (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Rights Resources Directory and Healthcare Action Toolkit, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Direct Action for Rights and Equality, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Delmarva Poultry Alliance, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - The Creative Coalition, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Coalition Collaborative, 1988-1996 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Dunlop Commission, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - GATT, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Good Jobs First, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Global Exchange, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Essential Action (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Free Time, Free People, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Fuerza Unida, Levi Strauss Campaign, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Frontlash, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Journal of Southerners on a New Ground, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Just Economics, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Jobs Now Coalition, Minnesota, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Job is a Right Campaign, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Jobs for All Coalition, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Jubilee, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Just Cause, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Labor Institute, Corporate Power and the American Dream, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Kentuckians for the Commonwealth, 1982-1996 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - The Kopkind Colony, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - "Justice, Do it Nike!" Oregon Coalition, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Labor Heritage Foundation (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Labor Cartoons and Citizen Soldier (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Labor Council for Latin America Advancement (LCLAA), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Labor Notes, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Labor Notes, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- E9: National Coalitions and Campaigns (Box 25)
  - Labor Page, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - NAFTA, File 2, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - National Campaign for Jobs and Income, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - National Coalition for the Homeless, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - National Center for Pay Equity, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National Employment Law Project, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - National Family Farm Coalition, 1993-1998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - National Organizers Alliance, The ARK, 1996-2000 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - National Rainbow Coalition Labor Network News (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - National Toxics Campaign, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - New Directions Worker Education Center (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Unite Guess Campaign, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - National Interfaith Committee For Worker Justice, Faith Works Newsletter, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Faith Works, 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - National Labor Community Coalition for Public Works Jobs, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights, Inc., 1995-2001 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - National Labor Rights Board, Workplace Organizational Rights, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - The NW Foundation of Community Organization, NW Directions, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - National Priorities Project, Are You Winning or Losing? (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - National Network for Immigrant and Refugee Rights, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Fast Track, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - FTAA, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Voice at Work Presentation (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Education and Labor, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Jobs with Justice Training, Orientation, 1998-2003 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Workers' Rights Board, Jobs with Justice Publications, 1997-2001 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Jobs with Justice Fundraising Manuals, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Workers' Rights Information, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Voice at Work Presentation, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Labor Publications, 1999-2002 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- F1: EFCA and FTAA (Box 26)
  - Global Exchange, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Free Choice, 2000-2007 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - FTAA, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - FTAA Information, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - S11 Reading, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 9-11 Statements, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Bi-National Perspective on Offshore Outsourcing, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - S26 Organizing Kit, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - A4 Media Clips, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - S26 Report to Press, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - 2002 FTAA, Immigrant Laws (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Citizens Trade Campaign (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - News clippings, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Jobs with Justice Economic Education, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Jobs with Justice Slideshow, NAFTA (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Slide Show "Talking Points", 1996 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Health Care, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Global Grassroots Justice, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - NTUI, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - ILWU Solidarity, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Boston Solidarity School, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - FT, FTAA Grant Agreement, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Training Curriculum (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Free Trade, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - FTAA, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - 'No NAFTA for the Americas', 2001 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - FTAA Education, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - WSF, WEF Press Clips, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Justice for Janitors, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Ohio NAFTA Documents, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - FTAA Materials, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - S26 Materials, CTA, Endorsers, Grid, Top 11, Organization Kit, Media Kit, Report, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Extra Articles S26, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Speeches, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - CAFTA, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - One on One Stop NAFTA (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Global Justice Strategic Session (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - NAFTA and Ohio (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Fair Trade, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- F2: Building JwJ Trainings; Building JwJ Misc Publications; MLK Cards; Global Justice Mapping Project (Box 27)
  - Pamphlets (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Building a More Powerful Movement for Justice, Labor-Community-Religious Coalitions (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Building Jobs with Justice Training, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Building Jobs with Justice Training, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Labor Publications, 2005-2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Reports and Sessions, 2012 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Bi-National Perspective on Offshore Outsourcing, A Collaboration Between Indian and US Labor, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Working Hard, Earning Less, The Story of Job Growth in America, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "Si, Se Puede" (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Workers' Rights Directory, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Jobs with Justice Press Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Jobs with Justice Healthcare Action Toolkit (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Worker Information, Interviews, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Comic, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Press Clipping, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Kentucky-Sonora Exchange (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - FTAA Quebec 4-Pager, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Sample Materials, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Sprint Actions Organizing Materials, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Tracking (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - National Alliance for Fair Employment (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Jobs with Justice Card, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    Contains transparency
  - Jobs with Justice, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Past Workers Rights Directories, Ad books, 1999-2006 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Communicating for Change, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Right to Organize Four-Pager, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Welfare Reform Confidential Comix (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - The Big Fix Comics and Information Sheet, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Pamphlets (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Workers' Rights Spreadsheets, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- G1: Sarita Gupta's Files (Box 28)
  - National Conference, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - USSF, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - "Another World is Possible" World Social Forum, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - New Trade Union Initiative Documents, 2000-2007 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    English and Hindi
  - The US Social Forum, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - The US Social Forum, National Planning Committee Meeting, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    December 19-22 2006
  - Itinerary for US Social Forum, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Jobs with Justice Documents, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Health Care Reports, 2001-2004 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Jobs with Justice Board of Directors, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - "A Generation of Resistance and Visionary Action", 2011 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - JwJ In Person Labor Coalition Meetings for Strategic Planning, 2008-2009 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Info on FTAA (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Leverage Wheel (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Workers'' Rights Plenary, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - LWIW Coalition, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Local Coalition Development, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - AFW 6 Steps, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Free Trade Area of America, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Employee Free Choice Act, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - S26 Localize the Movement for Global Justice, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - US Labor Against the War, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - States Rights and International Trade Booklet, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - The Inter-Alliance Dialogue and the Economic Meltdown Funnies, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - National Trade Union Initiative, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    October 2006
  - JwJ Healthcare for All, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Economic Recovery, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - FNTG, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Social Security No Match Letters, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    December 2007
  - Signal Workers Campaign, 2008-2009 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - AFW Beijing, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    June 21-22 2009
  - AFW, US Campaign Development, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - AFW Materials, 2007-2009 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - IAD, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - USSF Evaluation Team, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - GGJ Study, 2008-2010 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Grassroots Global Justice Documents, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Grassroots Global Justice Planning Documents, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - United States Social Forum, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    June 27 - July 1 2007. Atlanta, Georgia
  - GGJ Coordinating Committee, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - GGJ Resource Mobilization, 2008-2009 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Grassroots Global Justice, 2007-2008 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Grassroots Global Justice, 2008-2009 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Grassroots Global Justice Mapping Money, 1999-2009 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Grassroots Global Justice Documents, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Jobs with Justice Testimony, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Jobs with Justice Old Pamphlets, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Labor Health Care Movement, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Jobs with Justice Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - JWJ Strategic Planning, 2000-2006 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - JWJ Strategic Growth Fund, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Jobs with Justice Pamphlets and Newsletters, 2012 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Jobs with Justice Strategic Plan, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Jobs with Justice Implementation of Action Plan, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Strategic Planning, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Jobs with Justice Meeting Organizational Challenges, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Jobs with Justice Growth Reports, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 58)
- H1: Analia Penchaszadeh Files: Fundraising and Finance 2001-2007 (Box 29)
  - Fund Raising Training, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - September Fundraising Training, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 1998 Training: Applications and Logistics (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Portland Training, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    August 2001
  - Staff and Leader Gathering Healthcare Track, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Staff and Leader Gathering Overall, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - SLAP Pre-Conference, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Healthcare Pre-Conference, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Cross-Training MT/OR, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    June 1997
  - Educational Forum, Organize Strategic Retail Campaigns, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Interfaith Workshop, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - New Leader and New Staff Training, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - SGI Training, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    January 2002. Miami, Florida
  - History Session Training, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    July 1997
  - Right-to-Organize Training, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Highlander Right-to-Organize Training, Logistics Forms, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Right-to-Organize Case Studies, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Sustainable Growth Initiative Training, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    January 24 - 27 2002
  - National Strategic Planning 2002 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - National Charter, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - National Personnel Policy, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Local Jobs with Justice Sample Healthcare Work, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Social Security "No Match Letter" Case Studies, Cleveland JWJ, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Jobs with Justice Right to Organize Campaigns, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Jobs with Justice Campaigns, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Documenting and Promoting our Work, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Getting Help and Building a Sustainable Organization, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Mastering Your Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Making it Work Back Home, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Student Labor Action Project (SLAP), 2002 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Annual Meeting, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Anti-Oppression, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Women's Retreat, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Building Jobs with Justice Notebook Originals, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Student Labor Action Project Memos and News Releases, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Charter Application, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Base Building Project, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Season of Struggle, General, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - POC Gathering and Committee Notes, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous, 1991-2004 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Buffalo, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Healthcare Documents, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Healthcare Clips, 2002-2004 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - New Trade Union Initiative, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Religious Outreach, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    August 2004
  - Health Care Action Day Evaluations, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Health Care Action Day Materials, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - HCOP Boston, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Health Care Organizing Project Buffalo, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Health Care Press Clips, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Health Care Project, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - CEJ Healthcare Workshop (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Fundraising, General, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Fund for Just Society, 2000-2002 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - The Bydale Foundation, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - The Arca Foundation, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - America's Families United, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Immigrants and Labor (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Portland Training Binder, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    August 2 - 5 2001
  - Healthcare and the Nathan Cumming Foundation, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001-2005 (Box 29, Folder 61)
- H2: Analia Penchaszadeh Files: Fundraising and Finance 2001-2007 (Box 30)
  - Grassroots Global Justice Money, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Grassroots Global Justice Grants, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Fiscal Sponsor, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Fiscal Sponsor, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta Fiscal Sponsor, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Fiscal Sponsor, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Long Island Fiscal Sponsor, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Portland Fiscal Sponsor, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    December 2003
  - St. Louis Fiscal Sponsor, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Texas Fiscal Sponsor, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Washington State Fiscal Sponsor, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - The New World Foundation, Phoenix, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - St. Louis, 2002-2005 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - NYC Grant Proposals, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Veatch, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Woodbury Fund, D. Solomon, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Local Jobs with Justice Funding History, 2002-2004 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Immigrant Worker Rights, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Evergreen State College, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Utah 501c3, 2003-2004 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - IRS Information for 501c3, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Contracts, Letters, Insurance, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    June 14 2004
  - Union, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Proposals, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Union Appeal Letters, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Union Contributions, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Union Contributions, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Union Letters, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Presidents, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Union Requests, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Union Contributions, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Union Contributions Letter, Fundraising, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Jobs with Justice Union Funding Letters, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Union Membership and Support, Fundraising, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers Membership, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Union Tracking Mailings, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Tracking, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Tracking Forms, All, Templates, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Tracking, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Union Mailing on Tracking, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Fundraising 2000 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Sustainers Received, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Individuals, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Sustainers (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Individual Donors, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Contribution Thank You's, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Checks, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Ms. Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Union Community Fund, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - National Committee for Responsive Philanthropy, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - The Needmor Fund, 1999-2003 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Mertz Gilmore Foundation, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - The Heron Foundation, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - The Jewish Fund for Justice, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Albert A. List Foundation, 2000-2002 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - The McKay Foundation, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    September 19 2002
  - Jessie Ball DuPont Fund, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Neighborhood Funders Group (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Discount Foundation, 1993-1998 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - The Discount Foundation, 2001-2004 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - The Discount Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - French-American Charitable Trust, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Nathan Cummings Renewal, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 67)
    April 2003
  - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Common Stream (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Commonweal: A California Nonprofit Corporation, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    November 8 2000
- H3: Analia Penchaszadeh Files: Fundraising and Finance 2001-2007 (Box 31)
  - Fundraising Deadline (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - CFC Application, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Center for Labor Education and Research, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - National Fundraising 2001 Income (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - General Information on Foundation Fundraising, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Foundation Mailing, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Michael Moore Benefit "The Big One", 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Young Donors, Resource Generation, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Resource Generation, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Reimbursement Requests, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - National Network of Grant makers, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Veatch Program, 1991-1995 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - The Carnegie Foundation of New York, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Ben and Jerry, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    February 27 2002
  - Beldon Fund, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    July 5 2001
  - Common Counsel, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - CarEth Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Beirne Memorial Foundation, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - The Arca Foundation, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - A Territory Resuorce, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Angelina Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Academy for Educational Development, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Union Community Fund, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - UU Veatch Program, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Tides, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - The Stern Family Fund, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Fast Track Reports and Clips, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Solidago Foundation, 2000-2004 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - New World Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - New World, Phoenix, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Phoenix Fund, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    May 1998
  - The New World Foundation, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - The Norman Foundation, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    June 24 2002
  - Open Society Institute, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Ottinger Foundation, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Progressive Technology Project, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Philanthropic Collaborative, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    April 12 1999
  - Resist Funding Guidelines, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - The Pew Charitable Trusts, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Arca Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Shefa Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Elections, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Planning Committee, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Health Care, 1997-2001 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous Documents, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Canada, 1980-2007 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Sample Bylaws, 1999-2002 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Sample Foundation Proposals, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - NLRB Case Studies, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Diversity (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - 2003 Union Dues (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Fundraising MB Tasks, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - December 10 2003 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    Includes a CD
  - NLRB Actions Coordinator Lists, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 58)
    May 1993
  - NLRB Action Follow-Up, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - NLRB Planned Action Organization Kit, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - NLRB Union Presidents Statements on Activity, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Workers' Rights Board, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Last Folder (Box 31, Folder 63)
- H4: Analia Penchaszadeh Files: Fundraising and Finance 2001-2007 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous Strike and Union Documents, 2000-2003 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Field Team Fundraising, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - TAP, Oakland, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 3)